quizclothing.co.uk 2018-01-23

# Privacy and Cookies

Quiz is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and will not disclose any information except where it is vital to provide the services which we offer, including the process of arranging an item being sent to you. Your peace of mind is very important to Quiz and we will do all we can to maintain your privacy.

## 1THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

1.1 Registering with Quiz allows you to purchase our products and access the services being offered. The Information that we collect is:-

  * First Name
  * Last Name
  * Your Address
  * Email address
  * Telephone Number
  * Details of the method by which you wish to pay for the goods

1.2 We collect personal information to allow us to process and fulfil your orders.  Email addresses or telephone numbers collected allow us to contact you urgently if there is a problem with an order. Your information may also be provided to our third party service providers to complete the fulfilment of your order.

* * *

## 2COMMUNICATION

2.1 By registering with or becoming a customer of Quiz and by providing us with your email address, phone number and postal address you consent to receive communication in relation to our products, services and special offers that you may be interested in. This will usually be in the format of a newsletter. The information provided may also be used to communicate offers and products of third parties which you may be interested in.

2.2 All customers of Quiz can opt out of receiving marketing material sent by us or/and by third parties. To do this you can visit your account page by logging in and making the necessary changes. Newsletter subscribers can opt out by notifying us through email or by post.

* * *

## 3COOKIES

3.1 Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to store items in your Shopping Basket between visits. If you are a registered member of our website, we also use cookies to help us identify offers that may be of particular interest to you. We may then communicate those offers to you on the website or in accordance with your contact preferences. We do not track your use of any other websites. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your Shopping Basket and purchasing them.

* * *

## 4STORED INFORMATION & SECURITY

4.1 Quiz takes the security of your personal details extremely seriously. Security policies are designed to protect the personal details under our control. The Information that we have collected from you is maintained in a secure web server, which we believe to be a well protected and secure environment.

* * *

## 5USER ACCESS

5.1 Username and passwords are provided to you as a customer of Quiz. This allows you private access to information that we are holding, like the account information. You are able to access your online account anytime anywhere. If you wish to update, amend or delete any details, the online account gives you this access. Under the Data Protection Act 1998, you are also entitled to view any information we hold on you by paying a small fee. If any information on you is incorrect, please inform us immediately and we will make the necessary changes and contact you with confirmation of the changes.

* * *

## 6THIRD PARTIES

6.1 We will not pass or sell your information to our third party companies without your prior consent. Links to any third parties are provided to help and improve the service that we provide, however we have no control over the content of these websites and are not responsible for any material which may offend you. We will do our best to ensure that only relevant and quality links are provided.

* * *

## 7CONSENT

7.1 By becoming a customer of Quiz online you consent to the collection and use by Quiz online in the methods previously outlined.

* * *

## 8YOUR RIGHTS UNDER THE DATA PROTECTION ACT 1998

8.1 You have a right to access the personal data that we hold on you. If you would like to see a copy please send £10.00 and a written request to the Data Protection Manager, Quiz Clothing, 61 Hydepark Street, Glasgow, Scotland, G3 8BW quoting "Security and Privacy Enquiries". If you think the information we hold on you is incorrect please contact the Data Protection Manager quoting "Security and Privacy Enquiries".

* * *

## Cookies and your Privacy

Protecting the privacy of our users has always been a priority for Quiz. Recent changes in EU legislation means that we need to be clearer on the cookies we use on Quizclothing.co.uk.  

### So what are cookies?

Cookies are little text files that are automatically stored on your computer when you visit certain sites - including Quizclothing.co.uk. Cookies are used on all sites and do not harm your computer. For more information on cookies please visit: [www.whatarecookies.com/](http://www.whatarecookies.com/)

At Quiz we use cookies to keep track on what you have added to your basket and to remember this when you return to the site if you've not completed your purchase. You need to have cookies enabled to make a purchase.

The majority of web browsers have cookies enabled, but you can turn them off should you wish to. We don’t store personal information in these cookies but we do use them to improve the shopping experience.  

### Managing Cookies

Should you wish to remove cookies from your computer for Quizclothing.co.uk or for any other website then you can do in your browser settings.

Please note however, that if cookies aren't enabled on your computer then you will not be able to shop on Quiz. You will be able to browse through the site but won't actually be able to make a purchase as our checkout is reliant on the use of cookies.

To enable cookies on your computer you'll need to go to the web browser you are using and enable cookies. Below are instructions of how to do this for specific browsers.

**Internet Explorer for PC**

  * Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser
  * Select 'Internet Options'
  * Click the 'Privacy Tab'
  * Set your Privacy level to Medium or below. This will enable cookies.

**Firefox for PC**

  * Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser
  * Select the 'Privacy Icon'
  * Click on 'Cookies'
  * Select 'Allow site to set cookies'

**Safari for PC**

  * Click on the 'Cog icon' at the top of your browser
  * Select the 'Preferences' option
  * Click on 'Security'
  * Click the option that says 'Block third-party and advertising cookies'
  * Click 'Save'

**Google Chrome for PC**

  * Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser
  * Select 'Options'
  * Click on the 'Under the Hood tab'
  * Find the 'Privacy' section
  * Select 'Content' Settings
  * Select Allow Local Data to 'Set'

**Internet Explorer for Mac**

  * Click on 'Explorer' at the top of your browser
  * Select 'Preferences'
  * Find 'Cookies' under Receiving Files
  * Select 'Never Ask'

**Safari for Mac**

  * Click on 'Safari' at the top of your browser
  * Select 'Preferences' Option
  * Click on 'Security'
  * Click 'Accept Cookies'
  * Select 'Only from the site you navigate to'

**Mozilla/Netscape for Mac**

  * Click on 'Mozilla' or 'Netscape' at the top of your browser
  * Select 'Preferences'
  * Scroll down to 'Cookies' under the 'Privacy & Security' section
  * Select 'Enable Cookies for the originating website only'

**Opera for Mac**

  * Click on 'Menu' at the top of your browser window
  * Select 'Settings'
  * Select 'Preferences'
  * Select the 'Advanced Tab'
  * Select the 'Accept Cookies' option

To fully utilise all the features of Quizclothing.co.uk and to purchase products on the site, then you will need to enable cookies on your computer, tablet or smartphone. If you are accessing Quizclothing.co.uk through a smartphone then you'll need to check the settings of your handset to change your cookies preferences.  

### We use the following Cookies on Quizclothing.co.uk

**ac_shop, ac_aff_linkshare, ac_no_stats** – These cookies are used so that the shopping basket and checkout can operate correctly. They simply allow you to make a purchase.

**V1v4, V2v4, V3v4** \- These cookies are used to identify you when you are using our site. No personal information is collected.

**__utma, __utmb, __utmc, __utmz, __utmv** \- These are cookies set by Google Analytics, which allows us to analyse visitors to the site. Google analytic cookies do no collect personal data about visitors to our website.

**Peerius_rid, Peerius_ct, Peerius_sess, Peerius_user** – These are cookies set by a 3rd party provider called Peerius. They are used to provide a personalised, relevant and user specific shopping experience.

### Social Network Cookies

Sometimes you may like to 'share' content from Quiz via sites like Facebook, Twitter, Google+ or Pinterest. In doing so you may be sent cookies from these websites. We don't control the settings on these websites, so you'll need to check each site individually to ascertain their cookies policy.

For any further questions regarding our cookie policy please visit the contact us page.
